Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1984 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1984 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1984 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1984 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1984 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1984 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1986 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1986 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1986 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1986 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1986 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1986 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1987 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1987 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1987 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1987 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1988 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1988 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1988 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1988 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1988 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1989 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1989 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1989 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1989 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1989 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1989 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1989 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1989 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1989 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1989 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1989 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1989 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1990 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1990 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1990 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1990 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1990 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1990 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1990 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1990 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1990 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1990 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1991 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1991 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1992 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1992 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1992 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1992 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1992 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1992 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1993 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1993 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1993 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1994 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1994 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1994 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1994 [1 of 2] (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1994 [2 of 2] (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1994 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1994 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1994 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1994 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1994 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1995 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1995 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1995 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1995 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1995 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1995 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1995 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, September 1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, October 1995 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, November 1995 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, December 1995 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1996 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1996 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1996 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1996 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Classified employee matters, 1989-1991 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Cline, Walter N., 1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Coalition for balanced transportation, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: College of Education and Human Services (CEHS), 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Commencement speech delivered, James Buchanan, May 16, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Commonwealth Of Virginia, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Commmonwealth of Virginia, auditor of public accounts, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Commonwealth of Virginia, State Council of Higher Education, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Commonwealth of Virginia, Office of the Governor, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Commonwealth of Virginia, various departments including library, 1983-1992 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Community College education, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Compensation plan, teaching and research staff, 1980-1988 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Compliance with the Virginia indoor clean air act, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Congratulations, 1986, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, June 29, 1992-September 25, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, "Kids to College", 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, executive committee meeting, March 7, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: CUWMA executive committee meeting, November 21, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, presidential biographical information, circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Consortium of Universities, CUWMA board trustees meeting, December 5, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Consumer price index, circa 1988 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Cost of living, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Department of education, slate advisory committee, teacher education, 1980-1990 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Department of social work, 1989-1990 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Educational services agreement, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Faculty address, September 16, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Faculty address, September 4, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Faculty newsletter, Department of Foreign Language and Literature, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Faculty salary, March 1, 1989-April 10, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Faculty salary peer group, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Fairfax transport problems, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: First annual conference for the Northern Virginia economy, May 17, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: George Mason University foundation, November 28, 1984-October 1, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Greater Washington research center, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Stanley E., rector, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Stanley E., rector, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Stanley E., rector, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Stanley E., rector, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Stanley E., rector, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Health, sport, leisure studies, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: History of George Mason University [1 of 2], 1964-1986 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: History of George Mason University [2 of 2], 1964-1986 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Housing and residential life update, December 5, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Human resources key advantage, 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: IASIS (Institute for Advanced Study in the Integrative Sciences), 1991 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Institutes, NVI, November 19, 1991-October 22, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Institutes and public policy, 1990-1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Institutes and public policy, November 19, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Institutes and public policy, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: International student exchange program, 1979-1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Krasnow, annual report, 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Legislative, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Legislative dinner show, December 1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Letter to University community, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Letter to GWJ (George W. Johnson) after visiting schools, June 13, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Library matters, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1979-1996 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, December 12, 1984-January 26, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Northern Virginia (NoVA) Institute, July 30, 1991-December 5, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Northern Virginia (NoVA) Institute, May 30, 1991-July 24, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Northern Virginia (NoVA) Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, January 15, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, executive orders, 1980-1986 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, executive orders, 1989-1991 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, executive orders, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Office of the Governor, Richmond, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Parking complaints, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Partnership for education, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Peer group arguments, 1986-1989 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Recommendation letters, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Report of George Mason University library task force, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Report on student assessment, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Retirement, VSRS, financial, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Retirement letters, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Retirement responses, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Salaries, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Salary benchmarks, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Salary cost of living, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: School of Continuing and Alternative Learning, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Slide show, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Slides used for BOV (Board of Visitors) orientation, August 5, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV), 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) and General Professional Advisory committee (GPAC), 1994 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) meeting, October 4, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) reports, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: State Council of Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) show, September 2, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Student concerns, August 27, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Student concerns, (Chi Phi issue), 1994 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Student concerns, disabled student issues (coalition), 1994 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Tallwood, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Telecommunications, April 15, 1982-July 6, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Telecommunications, September 24, 1986-October 28, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Telecommunications, March 4, 1988-October 24, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Telecommunications, August 31, 1989-February 4, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Thank you letters, 1981-1985 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Thank you letters; memos; correspondence, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Thank you letters; memos; correspondence, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Thank you letters; memos; correspondence, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Transportation, 1986-1991 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Transportation in Fairfax county, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Transportation study final report, July 28, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Transportation study final report, August 1989 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: University Center, facilities, 1990-1992 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: University Center, Vice-President, administration, facilities, July 13, 1988-April 3, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: University Center, Vice-President, administration, facilities, July 1, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: University Center, Vice-President, administration, facilities, 1992-1994 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: The University future: Across the river and into the trees, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: University policies, sexual harassment, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Virginia Initiative economic bridge, 1990-1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Virginia's academic libraries in the age of information technology, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Virginia's department of employee relations counselors, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Virginia's department of personnel and training, 1981-1984, 1988-1991 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), 1992 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), 1992-1995 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC) board of directors, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC) board of directors, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC) and supporting the academic mission, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Wright State University, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Writing center program, 1993-1995 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Workshop on funding transportation, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents: Deposit receipts, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents: Financial statements, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Council on the environment, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Counseling center, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Crime right's week, April 1996 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Cultural diversity, 1990-1993 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Czarda, Larry [1 of 3], 1993 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Czarda, Larry [2 of 3], 1994 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Czarda, Larry [3 of 3], 1994 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Czarda, Larry: Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Czarda, Larry: Arena management proposals [1 of 2], 1984-1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)